const dayTwentyTwoQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Shaytan places his throne on ………………………",
    options: ["Air", "Water", "Fire", "Mountain", "Sky"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which Angel is in charge of vegetation and rains drop?",
    options: [
      "Angel Israfil",
      "Angel Mikail",
      "Angel Jibril",
      "Angel ‘Atid",
      "Angel Malik",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What are the types of Shirk?",
    options: [
      "Major and Minor Shirk",
      "Obligatory and Voluntary Shirk",
      "Shaitan and Human Shirk",
      "Forgiven and Unforgiven Shirk",
      "Belief and Disbelief Shirk",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the difference between Shirkul Akbar and Shirkul Asgar?",
    options: [
      "The later takes one outside the fold of Islam whereas the former does not",
      "The former reduces faith whereas the later does not",
      "The former takes one outside the fold of Islam whereas the later does not",
      "The later reduces faith whereas the former does not",
      "The former increases faith whereas the later reduces it",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Prophet Muhammad (May the peace and blessing of Allaah be upon him) said: 'Whoever swears with anything other than Allaah has already…………………………'",
    options: ["Succeed", "Disbelieve", "Sin", "Dead", "Swear"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Slaughtering in respect of somebody other than Allaah is ………………….",
    options: ["Minor sin", "Allowed", "Crime", "Major Shirk", "Minor Shirk"],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Is it right to eat from what was slaughtered to a holy man, if at all; name of Allaah was mentioned before slaughtering?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Destinies of each have been written by Allaah before He created heavens and earths about………………………… years.",
    options: ["50", "500", "5000", "50000", "500000"],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the man’s right on Allah?",
    options: [
      "He will punish not those who do not associate thing to Him",
      "To worship Him and not associate partner to Him",
      "To worship Him",
      "To praise Him",
      "To associate no partner to Him",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What will be the first food that dwellers of Paradise will take?",
    options: [
      "Fish",
      "Cow meat",
      "Dates",
      "Camel meat",
      "Extra-lobe of fish-liver",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Good dream comes from Allah and bad dream comes from …………………",
    options: ["Allaah", "Heaven", "Shaitan", "Azarail", "Hell"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the first major sign of the last hour?",
    options: [
      "Emergence of Dajjal",
      "Descend of ‘Issa peace be upon him",
      "A fire that will bring together the people from the east to the west",
      "Gog and Magog",
      "Rising of the sun from the west",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Does the Paradise and Hell fire exist?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What are the three basic things that are compulsory for everybody to know?",
    options: [
      "To know about our lord, His religion and His messenger (Prophet Muhammad peace and blessings of Allaah be upon him)",
      "To know about our lord, His angels and His messengers",
      "To know about Allah, His angels and His books",
      "To know about Allah, His messengers and His books",
      "To know about messengers, angels and divine revelations",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What are the three roots of worship?",
    options: [
      "Knowledge, action and patience",
      "Knowledge, practice and calling people",
      "Love, fear and hope",
      "Declaration, prayer and fasting",
      "Testimony, affirmation and action",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
];
export default dayTwentyTwoQuestions;
